Sebastian Javier Guzman

React FullStack Developer

Mar del Plata, Argentina (GMT-3) (+54) 9 2234498748 seba.guzman13@gmail.com https://linkedin.com/sebastian-javier-guzman https://github.com/sebaguzman13

React FullStack Developer with 2 years of experience, working with React, Java + SpringBoot and MySQL. I'm a curious person that strongly believe in team work and communication, and enjoys learning new things on my own and from other team members. My professional objective is to help develop enjoyable applications and get to know another cultures, that's why I'm currently looking for new challengues with international team members.

EXPERIENCE

Ensolvers,

Ampit — September, 2021 - Present

- Fix and create junit Tests for services and controllers implementing test containers and db dumps to reduce test cicles iteration times.
- Added Media player discriminator to handle player's display behavior.
- Updated chat and wallet summary class components to functional components. Reducing unnecesary re renders and requests.

Tech Stack: React, React Native, Java, Spring Boot, MySQL.

Ticketon — January, 2022 - July, 2022

- Purchase Flow implementation with ticket's booking and automated cancelation upon time limit reached, reducing amount of unfinished purchases.
- Worked with the UI/UX team to apply mock ups styles into the proyect's final results. Using Mateiral UI v4 to create base styled components to improve development speed.
- Mobile First responsiveness ensuranse and App Styles standarization.

Tech Stack: React, React Native, Java, Spring Boot, MySQL.

Alkemy, FullStack Developer — March, 2021 - August, 2021

- Helped setting up CRUD Redux store with Local Storage implementation to reduce unnecesary fetch calls.
- Updated application tables design for mobile viewports and homogenize styles and classes to improve readability.

Tech Stack: React, Redux, Tailwind CSS, Nodejs, Express, MongoDB.

PROJECTS

FrontEnd Developer (ENERGY <code>) - URL - 2020

Frontend bug fixing and manteinance on demand, as freelancer on real state management application.
React, CSS.

SKILLS

Programming Languages: <u>Intermediate:</u> Javascript, java; <u>Basic:</u> php.

Frameworks Tools: Intermediate: React, MaterialUI, bootstrap; Basic: React Native, Redux.

Data Base: Intermediate: MySQL; Basic: MongoDB.

Tools: liquibase, sass

Agile: Scrum

Languages: Fluent: English; Native: Spanish.

EDUCATION

Universidad Tecnoogica Nacional - Mar del Plata, Buenos Aires. Computer System's Technitian, Unfinished.

CERTIFICATIONS

Computer Programming with javascript - Coderhouse. 2021. Java POO Computer Programming - UCIP Mar del Plata. 2018. SoftSkills Online course - Accenture. 2021.